[
    {
        "question": "The psyche spacecraft is roughly the same size as:",
        "options": [
            "A football field",
            "A singles tennis court",
            "A car",
            "A bicycle"
        ],
        "answer": "b"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was Psyche discovered by?",
        "options": [
            "Albert Einstein",
            "Annibale de Gasparis",
            "Isaac Newton",
            "Galileo Galilei"
        ],
        "answer": "b"
    },
    {
        "question": "When did the Psyche spacecraft launch?",
        "options": [
            "October 13, 2023",
            "December 5, 2019",
            "August 21, 2000",
            "The Spacecraft has not launched yet"
        ],
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "The asteroid is located in the main asteroid belt between which two planets?",
        "options": [
            "Earth and Mars",
            "Mercury and Venus",
            "Mars and Jupiter",
            "Jupiter and Saturn"
        ],
        "answer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many solar arrays is the Psyche spacecraft comprised of?",
        "options": [
            "1",
            "2",
            "4",
            "10"
        ],
        "answer": "b"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is unique about the Psyche asteroid?",
        "options": [
            "It is rich in metal",
            "It is the largest asteroid that has been discovered",
            "It is composed mainly of ice",
            "It is located near Earth"
        ],
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where was the launch location for the Psyche Mission?",
        "options": [
            "Marshall Space Flight Center",
            "Stennis Space Center",
            "Lyndon B. Johnson Space Center",
            "Kennedy Space Center"
        ],
        "answer": "d"
    },
    {
        "question": "When will the spacecraft arrive at the Asteroid?",
        "options": [
            "Mid-2029",
            "End of 2026",
            "Mid-2035",
            "It has already arrived at the Asteroid"
        ],
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "How far will the Psyche spacecraft travel?",
        "options": [
            "100 miles",
            "100,000 miles",
            "1 million miles",
            "2.2 billion miles"
        ],
        "answer": "d"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where was the launch location for the Psyche Mission?",
        "options": [
            "Marshall Space Flight Center",
            "Stennis Space Center",
            "Lyndon B. Johnson Space Center",
            "Kennedy Space Center"
        ],
        "answer": "d"
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of new communication technology will the Psyche mission be testing?",
        "options": [
            "Solar",
            "Radio",
            "Laser",
            "Gravity"
        ],
        "answer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "The bus(body) is roughly the size of:",
        "options": [
            "A large airplane",
            "A small van",
            "A motorcycle",
            "A skateboard"
        ],
        "answer": "b"
    },
    {
        "question": "How much does the psyche mission cost?",
        "options": [
            "$1 million",
            "$150 million",
            "$850 million",
            "1.4 billion"
        ],
        "answer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Psyche Mission is led by which university?",
        "options": [
            "Arizona State University",
            "Harvard University",
            "University of Florida",
            "California Institute of Technology"
        ],
        "answer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "What will happen at the end of the Psyche mission?",
        "options": [
            "The spacecraft will stay in orbit around Psyche",
            "The spacecraft will come back to Earth",
            "The spacecraft will travel towards the sun",
            "The spacecraft will travel to another asteroid"
        ],
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the Psyche Gamma-Ray and Neutron Spectrometer?",
        "options": [
            "They detect and measure the remanent magnetic field of the asteroid",
            "They take images of Psyche to discriminate between metallic and silicate constituents",
            "They detect, measure, and map Psyche's elemental composition",
            "They measure Psyche's gravity field to high precision"
        ],
        "answer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the X-band radio telecommunications?",
        "options": [
            "They detect and measure the remanent magnetic field of the asteroid",
            "They take images of Psyche to discriminate between metallic and silicate constituents",
            "They detect, measure, and map Psyche's elemental composition",
            "They measure Psyche's gravity field to high precision"
        ],
        "answer": "d"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the Psyche Magnetometer?",
        "options": [
            "They detect and measure the remanent magnetic field of the asteroid",
            "They take images of Psyche to discriminate between metallic and silicate constituents",
            "They detect, measure, and map Psyche's elemental composition",
            "They measure Psyche's gravity field to high precision"
        ],
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of the Psyche Multispectral Imager?",
        "options": [
            "They detect and measure the remanent magnetic field of the asteroid",
            "They take images of Psyche to discriminate between metallic and silicate constituents",
            "They detect, measure, and map Psyche's elemental composition",
            "They measure Psyche's gravity field to high precision"
        ],
        "answer": "b"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many phases does the Psyche Mission consist of?",
        "options": [
            "One",
            "Three",
            "Six",
            "Fifteen"
        ],
        "answer": "c"
    }
    
]
